# **Dragos Oancea Zevri**

Senior Web Developer

I am a **Senior Web Developer**, who's been building websites for 10 years now. I am passionate about web technologies, constantly trying to learn new things and improve my skills.

websitehttp://dragos.cvolio.comemail addressoancea.dragosh@gmail.com

phone number +31615431926 location Amsterdam NH birthday March 25, 1980 marital status married

### Professional Experience.

#### Senior Web Developer

thispagecannotbefound.com - Amsterdam October 2011 - April 2013

#### Creating and Maintaining:

- Corporate websites
- FaceBook Applications
- Web Mobile Applications (Single Page Applications)
- Internal structuring

#### Senior Web Developer

Kubis Interactive - Bucharest July 2008 - October 2011

#### **Creating and Maintaining:**

- Promotional Brand Campaigns
- Corporate websites
- FaceBook Applications
- Intranet Applications
- Server Administrator (LAMP)

#### Senior Web Developer

Senior Interactive - Bucharest November 2005 - July 2008

#### **Creating and Maintaining:**

- Promotional Brand Campaigns
- FaceBook Applications
- Intranet Applications

#### Junior Web Developer

Mirabilis Media - Bucharest September 2003 - October 2005

- Maintaining high traffic websites
- Maintaining government website / internal applications
- Creating small websites / intranet applications;
- Server Administrator

### Education.

University "Politehnica" of Bucharest 1998 – 2004

#### Courses.

LEC LINE-EDUCATION-CENTER 2009

Advanced PHP course (2009), OOP, PDO with MySQL, POO Design patterns, XML & DOM, Streams & Networking, Web Services.

## ONLINE PORTFOLIO

dragos.cvolio.com

### Skills.

API'S **Programming** Markup / Styling / Data

Facebook **Javascript** ES 4x (X)HTML(4,5), CSS(2,3), Sass, LESS

php, javascript SDK's jQuery(UI/Mobile), Zepto, Backbone, Bootstrap, Foundation, Flat-UI **Twitter** 

JSON2(p), REST RequireJS, Handlebars, TweenMax php, javascript SDK's

Google PHP 5.x XML, XPath

Maps, Youtube, OAuth2, Analytics Codelgniter, Laravel, CakePHP LinkedIn, Echonest, Spotify, Tropo

Express, Meteor

**DBMS** SVN, Git, HG(mercurial) MySQL 5.x **Terminal** 

**Jenkins** MyISAM, InnoDB Sublime Text, Coda, Vim

**NoSQL** Grunt.js, Apache Ant **Querious/Sequel Pro** MongoDB

## Languages.

Apache 2.x, Nginx 1.x

Node.js 0.8~

1. Romanian - native

Versioning / Builds / Webservers

2. English - professional working proficienty

3. Dutch - elementary

#### Interests.

- new technologies
- gadgets
- guitar player
- traveler

Tools

Photoshop, Transmit